Guide to the Herbert Matter Papers
Department of Special Collections
- Series 9: Photographs Gifted from the Matter Family, 1.5 linear ft.
  - Subseries 9.12: Commercial
    - Shirley Temple doll head molds; [Folder 2].ND, 36105115667151; 8"x10": Stamped on back "Photo": and "Herbert Matter". (Othertype 407, Folder 2)
    - Jackson Pollock painting; [Folder 2].ND, 36105115667169; 11"x14" (Othertype 407, Folder 3)
    - Circular rotating drum; Motion study; Eames demonstration drum; 1946; [Folder 2].1946 ca., 36105115667177; 11"x14" (Othertype 407, Folder 4)
    - "Atomic head; Arts and Architecture cover December, 1946; [Folder 2].", 36105115667185; 16"x20" (Othertype 407, Folder 5)
    - "Film strips; Photogram; Fortune magazine cover July, 1948; [Folder 2].", 36105115667193; 11"x14": Slight tear along left edge near top: written on back in pencil "13" and is circled. (Othertype 407, Folder 6)